<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Food Recipes</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">296644168504789</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb296644168504789</string>
    <string name="Muttonkawab">spoon cumin powder
1 teaspoon dry mango powder (amchur)
1 teaspoon ajwain (carom seeds)
1 teaspoon chaat masala
½ teaspoon black pepper powder (optional)
Kashmiri red chili powder gives a nice red color to the food but is not spicy and hot. Instead of kashmiri red chilli powder, you can add 2 teaspoons of sweet paprika or ½ to 1 teaspoon of cayenne pepper.
    6. Add ½ teaspoon black salt and regular salt as per taste. If you do not have black salt, then skip it.
    . Begin to thread the veggies and paneer alternately on bamboo skewers. Before you begin to thread preheat oven at 230 or 240 degrees Celsius or 464 degree Fahrenheit for 15 to 20 minutes</string>
    <string name="Paneerbutter">1. Peel, rinse and dice 1 medium-sized onion in square shaped 1 to 1.5 inches pieces. Rinse and slice 1 small to medium sized capsicum (green bell pepper) in 1 to 1.5 inches pieces. You will need ½ cup each of onions and capsicum. Keep aside. You can also use tomatoes if you want.
     2. Crush 1.5 inches ginger and 6 to 7 small to medium sized garlic to a fine paste in a mortar-pestle. You will need 1 tablespoon of crushed ginger-garlic or 1 tablespoon of ready ginger-garlic paste.
    3. Slice 200 to 250 grams block or paneer into cubes or squares and keep aside. Best is to use homemade paneer.
    4. Put 200 grams hung curd (greek yogurt) in a bowl. With a whisk beat the curd lightly till smooth.
    5. Now add 1 tablespoons ginger garlic paste or 1 tablespoon crushed ginger garlic to the curd. Also add all the dry spice powders. Below you see the following Indian spice powders in clockwise order:

2 teaspoons kashmiri red chili powder
1 teaspoon coriander powder
½ teaspoon turmeric powder
½ teaspoon garam masala powder
1 teaspoon cumin powder
1 teaspoon dry mango powder (amchur)
1 teaspoon ajwain (carom seeds)
1 teaspoon chaat masala
½ teaspoon black pepper powder (optional)
Kashmiri red chili powder gives a nice red color to the food but is not spicy and hot. Instead of kashmiri red chilli powder, you can add 2 teaspoons of sweet paprika or ½ to 1 teaspoon of cayenne pepper.
    6. Add ½ teaspoon black salt and regular salt as per taste. If you do not have black salt, then skip it.
    . Begin to thread the veggies and paneer alternately </string>
    <string name="Muttonmasala">at 1 1/2 tablespoon ghee in another wok over high flame. When it gets hot, add ginger paste and garlic paste and fry it till the raw smell is gone.
add the fried onion paste and fry for a few seconds while stirring continuously. Add tomato puree and fry until the oil separates, stirring occasionally.
Add cashew paste and fry it again until the oil has slightly separates. Add finely chopped green chillies, beaten curd and mix well. Turn down the heat to medium and fry till the oil seperates, stirring occasionally.
In between, check if the chicken is cooked and become soft and tender, stir well.
When the oil separates from the gravy, add 1 cup of water to the gravy and mix well. Add salt as per your taste and mix well and let the gravy boil.
Check the chicken again, until now it is cooked if not cooked for some more time. when chicken is done, add chicken to the gravy along with all the masala in the wok and mix well.
Add garam masala, black pepper powder, chaat masala, fenugreek powder and 2 tablespoon cream and mix well. Turn off the gas.
Now to give it a smoked flavor, place a small bowl of steel in the center of the wok and put a piece of burning coal in it and pour a big spoonful of ghee on the burning coal, and cover the wok with a lid so that the smoke mixes in the chicken and gives it a smoked flavor. Keep this for 5 minutes.
Remove the coal bowl. Delicious chicken barra is ready.
Transfer the delicious chicken barra to the serving bowl and garnish it with fresh cream, kasuri methi powder, coriander leaves along with some lemon juice.
Enjoy it at your lunch or dinner with ROTI, Butter Naan or rice</string>
    <string name="Chickenbarra">Wash and clean the chicken. Take chicken in a large bowl, add red chili powder, turmeric powder, chopped green chillies, coriander leaves, ginger paste, garlic paste, pepper powder, garam masala, lemon juice, beaten yogurt, fried and onion Add salt, cinnamon powder and ghee and mix well to coat all the spices on the chicken.
Cover the bowl and keep the chicken to marinate for 1 hour.
Cook The Chicken

Heat 2 tablespoons ghee in a deep wok on high heat. When the ghee becomes hot, add the marinated chicken slowly and saute it for about 1-2 minutes on high flame while stirring continuously.
Cover the wok and cook the chicken until it becomes soft and tender, while stirring occasionally to prevent from sticking and burning.
Grind the fried onion and make a fine paste from it.
Boil tomatoes and grind them to make puree.
Heat 1 1/2 tablespoon ghee in another wok over high flame. When it gets hot, add ginger paste and garlic paste and fry it till the raw smell is gone.
add the fried onion paste and fry for a few seconds while stirring continuously. Add tomato puree and fry until the oil separates, stirring occasionally.
Add cashew paste and fry it again until the oil has slightly separates. Add finely chopped green chillies, beaten curd and mix well. Turn down the heat to medium and fry till the oil seperates, stirring occasionally.
In between, check if the chicken is cooked and become soft and tender, stir well.
When the oil separates from the gravy, add 1 cup of water to the gravy and mix well. Add salt as per your taste and mix well and let the gravy boil.
Check the chicken again, until now it is cooked if not cooked for some more time. when chicken is done, add chicken to the gravy along with all the masala in the wok and mix well.
Add garam masala, black pepper powder, chaat masala, fenugreek powder and 2 tablespoon cream and mix well. Turn off the gas.
Now to give it a smoked flavor, place a small bowl of steel in the center of the wok and put a piece of burning coal in it and pour a big spoonful of ghee on the burning coal, and cover the wok with a lid so that the smoke mixes in the chicken and gives it a smoked flavor. Keep this for 5 minutes.
Remove the coal bowl. Delicious chicken barra is ready.
Transfer the delicious chicken barra to the serving bowl and garnish it with fresh cream, kasuri methi powder, coriander leaves along with some lemon juice.
Enjoy it at your lunch or dinner with ROTI, Butter Naan or rice.</string>

    <string name="Paneertikka">1. Peel, rinse and dice 1 medium-sized onion in square shaped 1 to 1.5 inches pieces. Rinse and slice 1 small to medium sized capsicum (green bell pepper) in 1 to 1.5 inches pieces. You will need ½ cup each of onions and capsicum. Keep aside. You can also use tomatoes if you want.
     2. Crush 1.5 inches ginger and 6 to 7 small to medium sized garlic to a fine paste in a mortar-pestle. You will need 1 tablespoon of crushed ginger-garlic or 1 tablespoon of ready ginger-garlic paste.
    3. Slice 200 to 250 grams block or paneer into cubes or squares and keep aside. Best is to use homemade paneer.
    4. Put 200 grams hung curd (greek yogurt) in a bowl. With a whisk beat the curd lightly till smooth.
    5. Now add 1 tablespoons ginger garlic paste or 1 tablespoon crushed ginger garlic to the curd. Also add all the dry spice powders. Below you see the following Indian spice powders in clockwise order:

2 teaspoons kashmiri red chili powder
1 teaspoon coriander powder
½ teaspoon turmeric powder
½ teaspoon garam masala powder
1 teaspoon cumin powder
1 teaspoon dry mango powder (amchur)
1 teaspoon ajwain (carom seeds)
1 teaspoon chaat masala
½ teaspoon black pepper powder (optional)
Kashmiri red chili powder gives a nice red color to the food but is not spicy and hot. Instead of kashmiri red chilli powder, you can add 2 teaspoons of sweet paprika or ½ to 1 teaspoon of cayenne pepper.
    6. Add ½ teaspoon black salt and regular salt as per taste. If you do not have black salt, then skip it.
    . Begin to thread the veggies and paneer alternately on bamboo skewers. Before you begin to thread preheat oven at 230 or 240 degrees Celsius or 464 degree Fahrenheit for 15 to 20 minutes. Use only the top heating element while preheating as well as grilling. Soak or rinse the bamboo skewers before threading.</string>


    <string name="Hydrabadibiryani">Start by marinating the chicken. To make the marinade, mix 1 tsp caraway seeds (shahi jeera), 2 tsp ghee, 4 tsp ginger garlic paste, ½ tsp garam masala powder, 1 tsp coriander powder, ½ tsp cumin powder, 2 tsp red chili powder, 1 tsp turmeric powder, 2 tsp salt, 2 tbsp vegetable oil, 4 tsp green chili paste, and 2 tbsp lime juice in a large mixing bowl.
    Wash 1 pound (500 g) chicken and drain all the water. Add it to the bowl and mix well to coat it with the marinade.
    Take an 8-inch square cotton cloth piece and add 1 tsp caraway seeds, 2 whole black cardamoms, 2-3 whole green cardamoms, 2 flowers of javitri, 3-4 whole cloves, 1 tsp cumin seeds, 5-6 whole black peppercorn, 1 whole star anise, 2-inch stick of whole cinnamon, and 2 whole bay leaves in the center. Bring the ends of the cloth together and tie a knot to make a potli (bouquet garni).
   </string>



</resources>